-哥伦比亚职业杀手  -0.22中空弹
- Colombian hit squad. - .22 hollow point.
杀手转用子弹
It's an assassin's bullet.
也许有人想多分点钱
Somebody wanted a bigger piece of the pie for himself?
古斯塔夫·穆尼奥斯
Gustav Munoz.
看看这家伙能在我的城市里躲到哪儿去
Find out where in my city this guy thinks he can hide.
你们还记得八爪吧
You remember Pulpo, right?
他绑架过我儿子
He kidnapped my son.
他要把八爪从联邦监狱放出来
He's pulling Pulpo off MCC
用做诱饵抓古斯塔夫·穆尼奥斯
and using him as bait to draw Gustav Munoz.
你和那个"叛逆儿童"是怎么回事
What's up with you and rebel without a cause?
没什么啊  他都订婚了
Nothing. He's engaged.
我未婚妻
My fiancee.
着急娶媳妇啊
You're gonna tie the knot, huh?
我只是不想再做什么筹划了
I'm just sick of planning.
谁通知的内务部
Who called Internal Affairs?
你说我们是合作关系
You said this is gonna be a partnership.
合作也有很多种
There's a lotta different kinds of partnerships.
授予埃德文·斯蒂维尔  部门嘉奖
我手下有八个人
I have 8 people working underneath me
还有12名警察向我汇报工作
and another 12 cops that report to me.
你猜谁每天占用我一大半时间
Guess who takes up 75% of my time?
是你这个声音沙哑的混蛋
Your gravely-voiced ass.
你看看我们情报组的逮捕记录...
You know, I'd like to think the arrest record of my unit--
我做年度报告时
When I go in for my annual review,
只有你们跟内务部合作
it's measured on the number of arrests that you make
抓住的犯人才算数
working in conjunction with Internal Affairs,
到目前为止  只有一个
and so far, that number's one--
莫里斯·欧文斯
Maurice Owens.
我知道你整天混在街头巷尾
I know for a fact that you're out there on the street
跟一群人渣打交道
and you're rubbing shoulders with scum,
我可以想象你私底下偷偷
and I can only imagine how much money you've taken
收了多少黑钱
and not vouchered.
你是不是听谁胡说八道了  埃德文
Sounds like you're getting some fuzzy intel, Edwin,
这是不可能的
'cause that ain't happening.
我有个办法
I have a solution
可以让你的工作更高效点
as to how you can start working it off more effectively.
有个警探沾毒品
There's a narcotics detective
我们已经盯了一段时间了
that we've had our eye on for some time--
我不抓其他警察
I don't go after other cops.
我刚开始在这里跟你们做交易时
That was the first thing out of my mouth
第一条说的就是这个
when I made my little deal here,
所以不管你说什么
so you can shake your ass all you want.
这点是不变的
That ain't changing.
你要不多给我抓几个人来  你就死定了
You will give me more, or you will be gone.
这是给你的第一条也是最后一条警告
First and final warning.
亚当
Hey, Adam.
-伯吉斯  -怎么
- Burgess? - Yeah?
有时间吗  我想跟你说几句话
You got a second? Can I talk to you?
好啊
Sure.
你侄女怎么样了
How's your niece doing?
正在康复  谢谢关心
She's doing better. Thank you.
听我说  我知道
So listen, I know I've been
最近我一直在给你传达暧昧信号
sending some mixed signals lately.
不不  一个巴掌...
Oh, no. No, it takes two to...
拍不响...
mix signals, so...
我们不能这样了
Those are gonna stop.
-好吧  -我决定
- Okay. - Decided I'm gonna
真正一心投入到跟温迪的感情中
give my relationship with Wendy a real go, you know?
所以我和你说一声
I just wanted to tell you.
好  知道了
Yeah. Yeah.
我明白了
Absolutely. Of course.
-整件事我很抱歉  -不用
- I'm sorry about all this. - No.
-就这样  -好
- Okay. - Okay.
伯吉斯
Burgess.
-伯吉斯警官  -什么事
- Officer Burgess. - Yeah?
你去衣帽间
Go to the locker room,
使劲往脸上拍点冷水
throw some cold water on your face,
然后跟自己说三遍
then tell yourself three times
他从一开始就不属于你
he was never yours to begin with.
去吧
Go.
好
Okay.
你好  我找艾琳·琳德赛
Hi, I'm looking for Erin Lindsay.
请问你是
Are you?
我是他的老朋友  我叫查理
I'm an old friend. My name's Charlie.
留下你的姓名和联系方式
You can leave your name and number.
我会通知她的
I'll make sure she gets the message.
好了
Here you go.
你姓什么  查理
You got a last name, Charlie,
还是你就想神神秘秘的
or is this a Madonna-type deal?
她知道我是谁
She'll know who I am.
代我跟她说声好久不见
Tell her it's been a while.
八爪要出来的事有新消息吗
Hear anything more about Pulpo getting pulled out?
很显然他提出了一系列无理的要求
Apparently he's got an unreasonable list of demands
否则不肯合作
before he agrees to cooperate.
他还是在监狱里安全
Yeah, well, he's safer in prison.
我们这里有内奸  兄弟
We got a rat in here, bro.
掌管了情报组你以为会怎样
What did you think was gonna happen when you got this unit?
他们会这么放过你吗  不管你以前的种种
They'd just leave you alone; with your history?
我没想到他们会这么明显地来对付我
I didn't think they'd be so obvious about it.
我是博伊特
Go for Voight.
我是佩里  古斯塔夫·穆尼奥斯回来了
It's Perry. Gustav Munoz is back.
他又在城里犯事了
He struck again across town.
这是穆尼奥斯干的
This was Munoz.
我们在楼上发现了证据
We got proof of it upstairs.
这里有不少粉儿啊
Moving a lot of dope out of here.
各位  发现了一颗哑火的子弹
Hey, fellas. Found a misfired bullet.
是0.22中空弹
It's a .22 hollow point,
跟我们在二三会藏匿窝点找到的一样
Same as we found at the Two-Three stash house.
取证室快速检验了一下指纹
Crime lab did a rush on the prints.
跟古斯塔夫·穆尼奥斯的相符
it's a match for Gustav Munoz.
怎么找到这个家伙
Where are we finding this guy?
他的通缉令到处都有
Well, we got his face everywhere.
移民海关总署  扫黑部门
ICE, anti-crime--
所有部门都在找他
Every department is looking for him.
我还以为这家伙就是个拿钱干活的杀手
Look, I thought this guy was just a hired assassin.
不是的  局长
Not quite, Commander.
穆尼奥斯想把大权拿到手
Munoz is going for a full-on power grab.
他想当老大
He wants to wear that crown.
-穆尼奥斯以前不是八爪的手下吗  -是
- I thought Munoz was working for Pulpo; yes or no? - Yes.
局长  八爪已经同意全面配合我们了
Commander, Pulpo has agreed to cooperate with us fully.
我们可以问问他穆尼奥斯的情况
We can ask him about Munoz,
了解他的习惯  他的作案手法
what his habits are, what his behavior patterns are.
那他为什么还在监狱里
So why is he still in prison?
因为他不断提出各种条件...
Because he has a lot demands he keeps adding on--
去搞定
Look, make the deal!
你自己看看
Look around you!
我们已经等太久了
We already waited too long.
现在还有谁觉得
Now anybody else still think
不能和八爪合作的就举手
it's a bad idea to work with Pulpo,
看我不把他打得满地找牙
raise your hand so I can see who to punch in the mouth.
我觉得这简直是疯了
I think it's insanity.
你把这事儿处理好
You run this operation.
你给我确保
You are gonna make sure that Pulpo
八爪安全地进出监狱  懂吗
gets in and out of prison safe, you understand that?
你可以选择照我说的做
And you gonna keep your head on straight
也可以选择滚回去休息几天
or you gonna take some vacation time.
这两者我都可以接受
Either way is fine with me.
我知道大家都很愤怒
I know emotions are high.
八爪和他的走狗害死了我们一个同事
Pulpo and his men cost us one of our own,
还差点害死了我们一个同事的亲人
nearly cost us a family member.
但既然你们当了警察
But if you got into this profession
还指望不和混蛋打交道的话
expecting not to deal with scumbags,
那就是入错行了
you got into the wrong line of work.
去吧
Go ahead.
听着
Listen...
在其位  谋其职
This is us doing our job.
安东尼奥
Antonio.
这不是古斯塔夫·穆尼奥斯吗
Yes. Gustav Munoz.
是个很坏很坏很坏的人哟
Bad, bad, bad person.
如果能让他伏法可真是件好事呢
It'll be good to get him off the streets.
他在哪里
Where is he?
先谈生意
Business first.
我得确保我提的要求都得到满足了
I need to make sure my deal is done.
之后  我任凭你们使唤
After that, I'm at your service.
我想看看你们许诺了他什么
I want to see what you're giving him.
解除单独监禁
Out of solitary,
向他在监狱的账户里打钱  延长放风时间
money to his commissary account, extra yard time...
好的
It's all right.
允许配偶探访
Conjugal visits?
他有女人吗
Has he got a girl on the side?
找出来  我们要利用一切可以利用的资源
Find out. We can use whatever leverage we can get.
好的  我认识一个人
Yeah, okay. I know just the guy.
他是我去年逮捕的一个黑客
He's a hacker I busted a year ago.
他被软禁在家
He's under house arrest.
很好  出发
Perfect. Go.
穆尼奥斯
Munoz.
你大概知道  我还是个罪犯
As you may know, I'm still a criminal,
一个犯罪团伙的首领  对吧
a shot caller-- Yes?
在监狱那些人的眼中就是如此
To the eyes of the people in prison,
正因如此  假借手术之名
which is why the idea of pulling me out
把我从狱里弄出来真是太聪明了
for a fake surgery was so smart.
谢谢了  拜尔登警督
Thanks for that, Lieutenant Belden.
我身体里摘掉的那个部分用英语怎么说来着
How do you say in English what I'm getting removed?
胆囊
Gallbladder.
是的  西班牙语里面叫"Vesicula Biliar"
Yes. Vesicula biliar in espanol--
穆尼奥斯
Munoz.
就现在
Right now.
当然了
Of course. Um...
我需要一部手机  麻烦了
I'm gonna need a cell phone, por favor.
-别管  -我也不知道
- Leave it alone. - I don't know.
情报部里面所有人都会觉得我是个
Everyone in intelligence is gonna think
没法控制自己少女情怀的小姑娘
I'm some pie-eyed little girl who can't control her crushes.
不  是鲁塞克做得不对
Naw. Ruzek was playing where he shouldn't have.
不是他的错
It wasn't his fault.
警长  能给我们几把钥匙吗
Sarge, can we get some keys?
走吧
Let's go.
琳德赛
Hey, Lindsay.
今天有人来找过你
Somebody stopped by for you today.
-是吗  -他说他叫查理
- Yeah? - Said his name was Charlie.
有点小性感
Kind of hot.
身上有香烟和黑色达卡香水的味道
Smelled like cigarettes and Drakkar.
他说你们是老朋友
Said he knew you from a long time ago.
走吗
You coming?
话说查理是谁
So who's Charlie?
我原来一起鬼混的一个人
He's a... he's a guy I used to run with.
还是说你从他身边逃跑了
Run with or run from?
我有分寸
I got it handled.
你好啊  乔尼
What's up, Johnny?
这是琳德赛警探
This is detective Lindsay.
你好
How's it going?
我没做坏事  警探
I haven't done anything, Detective.
天呐
Good lord...
你不是因此在一个治疗师那里接受治疗吗
I thought you were working with a therapist for that.
偶尔会复发
I relapse sometimes.
他一开始是黑进一些色情网站
He started by hacking into porn sites...
-显然  -然后是政府数据库
- Clearly. - and that became government databases.
我只是  只是想看看自己到底有多少能耐
It was just to... to see if I could do it.
我们在调查一个叫做八爪的人
We're looking for a guy named Pulpo.
他的真名是亚德勒斯·迪亚斯
His real name is Adres Dias.
快来给我好好推演一下
Do one of your algorithms.
我们在寻找一些大家都忽视了的细节
We're looking for something everyone missed.
-开始吧  -那就违反了
- Go. - That'd be a violation
我假释的条件啊
of the conditions of my parole.
好吧
Okay.
但我要我自己的兄弟
But I want my own guy.
因为我就是这么说的
Because I said so.
他叫蒂科  你可以相信他
His name is Tico. He can be trusted.
好的  我得挂了
Okay. Hey, I got to go.
警卫要过来了  我得把手机藏起来
Guards are gonna come soon, and I gotta hide the phone.
好
Bueno.
[西语]
你派过去的这个蒂科是谁
Who's this Tico you're sending over?
你啊
You.
我建立的这个系统会对照检索
This program I built will cross-reference
美国国家安全局  联邦调查局
NSA, FBI,
中央情报局和国土安全部的数据库
CIA, and DHS databases.
八爪  亚德勒斯·迪亚斯
Adres "Pulpo" Dias.
有几个手机都与他相关
There are several phones I can link to him.
他在今年早些时候用这部手机
He called this one home on chicago's south side
给他在芝加哥南边的家里打了144次电话
144 times earlier this year.
就在他被情报部抓住之前
Right before he got pinched by intelligence.
把地址告诉我
Get me that address.
拉丁折扣广场
The Latin Discount Plazas.
在给定的时间内  装载毒品的联结车
At any given time, a tractor trailer full of drugs
可能停在这30个商店的任意一个门口
is being dropped off at one of these 30 malls.
警察永远不知道是哪一个
The police never knows which one.
毒品交易者们也不知道
Neither do the traffickers.
这样一来  如果有人被捕
That way if anybody gets arrested,
就不会有人把警察们引回老巢了
nobody can lead the cops back to the bosses.
但我的线人知道
But my connection knows,
他说今天有一批货会从印第安纳运来
and he says there's a shipment coming from Indiana today,
那我们就开始行动吧
and so here we go...
安东尼奥去和我兄弟接头
Antonio goes to meet my guy.
贝尼托·瓦达拉  "牛仔哥"
牛仔哥[西班牙语]
El Vaquero--
就是牛仔的意思  如果你们想知道的话
The cowboy, if you will.
牛仔哥会让你开车
El vaquero will give you the truck to drive.
马克斯·罗伯斯会和你接头
At the pick up will be Marcos Robles.
马克斯·罗伯斯
罗伯斯是负责这些毒品的高级头目
Robles is a high-level capo who's in charge of these drugs,
而就在那里
and it will be there,
女士们先生们请注意
damas y caballeros,
古斯塔夫·穆尼奥斯会去取他的分成
where Gustav Munoz will be to get his cut.
通缉中  古斯塔夫·穆尼奥斯
瓮中捉鳖  易如反掌
Easy as uno, dos, tres.
好了  过来
Hey, come here.
他说的所有名字都对得上
All the names match, so...
都有厚厚的案底  尤其是罗伯斯
pretty long sheets, especially with Robles.
都是哥伦比亚裔  所以挺合理的
All Colombian descent, so pretty legit.
你能行吗
You up for this?
我可以找别的警察来做卧底
I can pull another cop to go undercover.
我来吧
I'll do it.
是吗
Yeah?
你的西语说得怎样
How's your Spanish?
不好
No bueno.
穆尼奥斯认识你
Munoz knows what you look like.
你俩面对面动过手
You two went to fisticuffs.
我来吧
I'm doing it.
这样的话一旦出了事
That way if it goes south,
我也有理由好好教训八爪
I have an excuse to break Pulpo's neck.
如果事情没你说的那么易如反掌
This goes any different than uno, dos, tres--
用不着威胁我
No need to finish your threat, okay?
我很清楚自己的处境
I completely understand the situation I'm in.
安东尼奥
Antonio.
你见到牛仔哥的时候
When you see the cowboy,
告诉他八爪祝他生日快乐
tell him that Pulpo says happy birthday,
他就会知道你是自己人
then he'll know you're good.
你好
Que pasa?
我是蒂科
I'm Tico.
八爪祝你生日快乐
Pulpo says happy birthday.
我以前没见过你
I've never seen you before.
现在你见到了
Now you have.
把外套脱了
Open your shirt.
别紧张
Take it easy.
脱掉
Open it.
把外套脱掉
Open your shirt.
各就各位  准备冲进去
All right, get ready to move in.
你疯了吗
Are you out of your mind?
我不知道你是谁
I don't know who you are,
能证明你身份的只有一个名字
and all you got is a name.
我表亲和八爪
I'm the cousin of the guy
一起在斯泰特维尔监狱里
who's on Pulpo's tier at Stateville.
负责保护他
The one who gives him protection.
不如我告诉我表亲你用枪对着我
How 'bout I tell my cousin you pulled a gun on me,
等八爪出院回来
and as soon as Pulpo's back from the hospital,
他必死无疑
he slits his throat,
你觉得下一个死的会是谁
and guess whose throat is next?
抱歉
I'm sorry.
你早该道歉了
You damn well better be.
那么  就此一笔勾销
Entonces...estamos bien?
好吧
Si.
现在该怎么办
Okay. So now what?
安东尼奥·道森  真有你的
Antonio Dawson, baby.
小村折扣商场
再次向你道歉
Again, I'm sorry.
没事
Don't sweat it.
准备出发
Wheels up.
-琳娜·奥齐亚吗  -我是
- Lina Ochoa? - Yes?
我们是琳德赛和霍斯特德警探
Detectives Lindsay and Halstead.
我们有几个问题想问你
We have a couple questions to ask you.
什么问题
What about?
你认识一个叫亚德勒斯·迪亚斯
You know someone by the name of Adres Dias,
绰号"八爪"的人吗
goes by Pulpo?
老天  别和我提他
Oh, God, don't remind me.
你是怎么认识他的
How do you know him?
我们在夜店见过一次
We met in a club once.
我当时真不该对他那么好
I made the mistake of being nice to him.
我们发现他经常给你打电话
We noticed that he called you a lot,
大概有144次
like, 144 times.
是的  因为他是疯子
Yeah, 'cause he's crazy.
我觉得他想杀我
I would've taken out a restraining order against him
所以对他申请了禁令
if I didn't think he'd kill me.
他最近联系过你吗
Have you had any contact with him recently?
当然没有
Hell no.
他不会是越狱了吧
Don't tell me he's out.
没有
No.
没有  我们只是随便问问
No, we're just checking.
那就好  让他把牢底坐穿吧
Good. Let him rot in prison.
好的  感谢你的配合
Okay. Thank you for your time.
妈妈
Mama?
祝你们好运
Good luck.
孩子真可爱
Cute kid.
小村折扣商场
[西语]
钥匙
Keys.
你在这里等着
You stay here.
我看到罗伯斯了
I got an eye on Robles.
带着黑帽子  穿着带帽黑色皮夹克
Black hat, black leather jacket with a hoodie.
不过没看见穆尼奥斯
No sign of Munoz though.
他走了
He's on the move.
你跟我在这等
Hey, you stay here with me.
罗伯斯匆忙离开
All right, Robles is leaving in the rig.
跟着他
Follow him.
明白
Copy.
别难过了
Hey, quit beating yourself up.
没人会说你闲话
Nobody's gonna judge you.
小打小闹而已  谁在意呢
It's birds and bees. Who cares?
你说得对
You're right.
是的  我要重新开始
Yeah, I just-- I got to get back on the horse.
-这才是我该做的  -没错
- That's what I got to do. - Yes.
-是啊  -这么想就对了
- Yeah. - There you go.
而且我有好多对象可以介绍给你
And I got plenty of guys I could set you up with.
好啊  只要有工作的就行
Okay, as long as they have a job.
算了吧  有没有工作都行
You know what? No, I don't care.
我要去约会
I just... I got to go on a date.
只要吃饭不用我买单就行
As long as I don't have to buy dinner.
算了吧  我买单也行
You know what? I'll buy dinner.
收到报警  有人中枪倒地
We have a call of persons down.
请前往1916号基辅桑拿
Respond to Kiev Sauna, 1916.
-不许动  -芝加哥警署
- Freeze! - Chicago PD!
-举起手来  -转身
- Get your hands up! - Turn around!
趴地上
On the ground!
转身
Turn around!
转身  听到了吗
Turn around! You hear me?
跪下
Get down!
他有枪
Gun!
把手放下  穆尼奥斯在哪里
Put your hand down. Where's Munoz?
他们就这么走进来开枪杀人
They just walk in here and start shooting.
看这情景熟悉吗
Look familiar?
子弹类型
The bullet type,
近距离瞄准  一枪爆头
point-blank shots to the head.
你看见开枪的人了吗
Did you see the shooters?
他们没看见我
They didn't see me.
里面有他吗
Was he one of them?
古斯塔夫·穆尼奥斯  他在来的路上了吗
Gustav Munoz, he on his way?
穆尼奥斯  他来这里干什么
Munoz? Why would he be here?
为了来拿他那份钱  别跟我装傻
For his cut. Don't act stupid with me.
我可没跟你胡闹
I'm not playing around.
如果我看见古斯塔夫·穆尼奥斯  我会勒死他
If I saw Gustav Munoz, I'd strangle him.
他也会想要勒死我的
He'd try and do the same to me.
他不在这儿
He's not here.
各位
Guys.
两位乌克兰黑社会的高层
Two high-ranking Ukrainian mobsters
刚在城市另一边的一家澡堂被处决般的杀死了
were just killed in a bathhouse across town execution-style.
目击者认出穆尼奥斯是开枪的人
Witness I.D.'d Munoz as the shooter.
别告诉我我们刚被八爪给耍了
Don't tell me we just got worked by Pulpo.
出什么事了  没抓到穆尼奥斯吗
Que paso? No Munoz?
他肯定不会出现在那里  你很清楚
He was never gonna be there, and you know it.
你让我们白忙一场
You sent us on a goose chase
借我们的手除去你贩毒集团的竞争对手
to take out your rival faction within the cartel.
什么  不不不不
What? Nah, nah, nah, nah.
你  你胡说
That is-- that's crazy.
我真以为穆尼奥斯会去那儿  真的
I thought Munoz was gonna be there, I promise.
但即便这样  拜尔登警督跟我说
But even so, Lieutenant Belden here
你们缴获了至少一百千克的可卡因
told me you removed at least 100 kilos
还有一些非法武器
of cocaine from the street, recovered illegal weapons,
还有成千上万贩毒的黑钱
and hundreds of thousands of dollars in drug money.
总体来说  也不是一无所获嘛
I mean, all in all, not a wasted trip, yes?
我让你们收获这么大
Which I believe, uh...
给我买台新电视吧
is worth a new TV for me.
这是部分私下交易  没写出来
Part of our side deal. Wasn't in the paperwork.
滚出去
Get out.
别嚣张  博伊特
Turn it down a notch, Voight.
滚出去  要不我揍扁你
Get out or I will throw your ass out.
各位  别打啊
Hey, guys, come on!
冷静  博伊特  住手
Calm down, Voight! Stop--hey!
别闹了
Knock it off.
算了吧
Let it go.
局长  现在让我来负责吧
Commander, let me run point now.
八爪不信任这两个人  不想跟他们合作
Pulpo doesn't trust these two as far as he can throw 'em.
局长  你不是想把这个疯子放出来吗
Commander, you wanted this lunatic out.
现在他就在这
Here he is.
他一直在耍我们
He has been playing us.
他会继续耍我们  直到他恢复自由身
He will continue to play us till he is hanging off a ledge.
让我跟他单独待十分钟
Give me ten minutes alone with him.
-就十分钟  -你知道我不能让你这么做
- Ten minutes. - You know I can't.
你先等等
Not now!
有发现了
We got something.
这是八爪的妻子和儿子奥齐亚
This is Pulpo's baby mama and son, Osberto.
她是自愿来这儿的吗
She here 'cause she wants to be here?
不是  我们威逼利诱的
No. We leaned on her.
她有酒驾案底
She's got a failure to appear off a DUI.
或许可以假装把她关起来
Maybe played up possible jail time.
你来看孩子
You watch the kid.
能跟我走一趟吗  女士
Can you come with me, please, ma'am?
看来我们俩要独处
Looks like it's just gonna be me and you
一会儿了  小朋友
for a while, little buddy.
我妈妈有麻烦了吗
Is my mom in trouble?
外面有一个坏人  我们想阻止他
There's a bad man, and we're trying to stop him
继续干坏事
from doing more bad things,
而你妈妈在帮助我们
and your mom's helping us.
好吧
Okay.
好吗
Okay?
没事的
It's all right.
好吗
Okay?
-亚德勒斯  -没事的  宝贝
- Adres? - Hey, it's okay, baby.
一切都会好的
Everything's gonna be okay.
要是你儿子有个在牢里的妈妈
Be a shame for your kid to grow up
那得多丢人啊
with a mother in prison.
领养体系对孩子的成长可不好
The system isn't good for any child.
你不能这么做
You can't do that.
你绑架过我儿子  我可没意见也带走你的
You took my son. I have no problem taking yours.
亚德勒斯  别让他们把我们的儿子带走
Adres, please don't let them take our baby away.
淡定  没事的  淡定
Hey, it's okay. Hey.
放过她和我儿子
Leave her and my son alone
我就告诉你穆诺斯的下一个目标
and I'll tell you Munoz's next target.
如果你的情报属实
Well, if your information's good,
或许我们还有的商量
maybe we can work something out,
但这是你最后的机会了
but this is your last shot.
我明白
I understand.
在我说之前
All I need before I tell you
你必须要先答应我个新条件  就是琳娜
is to see my new deal that states that Lina and my son
和我的儿子不会被起诉
will be free from prosecution--
亚德勒斯
Adres!
拜尔登  我必须要见到白纸黑字
Elden, I need to see it in writing!
拜尔登
Belden!
等等  等等  好吧
Hey! Hey, okay!
好吧
Okay!
Okay.
-继续说  -穆尼奥斯
- Okay, what? - Munoz.
他会去耶稣升天节
He's gonna be at the Festival de L'ascension.
你听说过的  对吧安东尼奥
You've heard of it, right, Antonio?
在亚拉贡宴会厅举行
It's at the Aragon ballroom.
明天开始
It starts tomorrow.
没错
That's right.
有一个纽约来的男人
There's this man from New York.
高层人士
He's a high-level man.
叫弗朗西斯科·埃雷迪亚
His name is Francisco Heredia.
穆尼奥斯知道他会去过节
Munoz knows he'll be at the festival,
穆尼奥斯会去那儿杀他
and Munoz will be there to kill him.
这是穆尼奥斯的最后一个任务了
This is the final piece of the rompecabezas for Munoz.
有个女的五岁时就进了领养体系
There's a real bitch getting into the foster care system
现在是个妓女
at five years old.
我调查过很多类似的案子
I've investigated a lot of these cases.
重点就在于你几年后才会得知
The thing is, you just never know what happens
这些孩子受了多少罪
to some of these kids until years later.
我保证这次是真的
I promise you this is the truth.
你怎么确定埃雷迪亚会去那里
How do you know for sure Heredia will be there?
明天是他双胞胎女儿的生日
It's the birthday of his twin girls.
她们是在这出生的  而他很迷信
They were born here, and he's very superstitious.
每年  他和他的妻女
Every year he, his wife, and his twin girls
都会去参加节日的首庆
go to first day of the festival.
埃雷迪亚一死
Once Heredia dies...
整个集团就是穆尼奥斯和他的人的了
Munoz and his men will have sole control over the cartel.
让所有人早上八点来这里
Tell everyone to be here at 8:00 A.M.
走
Let's go.
博伊特  我现在就要见我儿子
Voight, I want to see my son now.
不行
No.
求你了  拜尔登
Please! Belden!
等我们抓到穆尼奥斯  你就能见你儿子了
We catch Munoz, you can see your son.
我向你保证
You have my word.
早上八点  换好衣服准备出发
8:00 A.M. Be suited up and ready to go.
-我们要相信八爪吗  -杰常是怎么说的来着
- And we believe Pulpo? - What is it Jay likes to say?
矮子里面拔高个  别无他法了
He's the best of a lot of bad options.
所以他说什么我们都信吗
So we're just supposed to take his word for it
即便他曾经骗过...
even after he lied--
你以为我愿意跟那个混蛋合作吗
You think I want to be dealing with this prick?
每一天  我看向桌子的那边
Every day I look across the desk
都会看到我搭档曾经坐过的椅子
and I see a chair where my partner used to sit,
都是因为他  她不在了
and she ain't here because of him.
亲爱的
Hey, baby. Hey.
怎么了
What's wrong?
来这边  进去
Come here. In here.
我一直在打你电话
I've been trying to call you.
我知道  对不起
Yeah, I'm sorry.
我正忙着处理案件
I've been swamped with this case.
有时是会这样的
It's gonna get like this sometimes.
我想去和我家人一起住一段时间
I think I'm gonna stay with my folks for a little bit.
-出什么事了  -亚当  这里不适合
- What's going on? - Adam, this isn't the place
谈这个话题  但我不知道
to have this conversation, but I never know
什么时候才能见到你
when I'm gonna see you.
你和在警校时不一样了
You're not the same as when you went into the academy,
这个组里有些东西改变了你
and something about this unit has changed you.
阿特沃特
Atwater, hey.
你看到伯吉斯了吗
You seen Burgess?
干嘛
Why?
"干嘛"是什么意思
What do you mean "Why"?
让她自己静一静吧  伙计
Just leave her alone, man.
你少多管闲事了
You need to mind your own business.
听着  我不在乎你在楼上工作
Listen, I don't care that you work upstairs.
我也不在乎你头衔高过我
I don't care that you outrank me.
你已经大大扰乱她的情绪了
You messing with her head too much.
所以你得放过她
So either you leave her alone,
否则你我就得好好谈谈了
or me and you gonna have to get into it.
好吧  我知道了
All right, man, you got it.
说得有理
Fair enough.
谢谢
Oh, thank you.
艾琳
Erin.
查理
Charlie.
我回来了
I'm back.
我...
I'll, uh...
我们明天见吧
I'll see you tomorrow.
你确定
You sure?
是
Yeah.
好吧
Okay.
没事
I'm good.
不抱我一下吗
No hug?
来吧  来吧
Come on. Come on.
很好
All right.
你的警徽呢
Okay, where's the badge?
看到警徽我才相信
I'm not gonna believe it till I see the badge.
拿出来吧
Come on.
我还是无法相信
I still don't believe it.
人生真是奇妙  对吧
It's funny how life works out, huh?
你不该来芝加哥的  查理
You're not supposed to be in Chicago, Charlie.
都这么久了
It's been long enough.
我很想大家
I missed everybody,
也很想你
missed you,
还有...
and, uh...
我不需要多作解释
Well, I don't need to explain myself.
我就是想回来了
I wanted to come back.
你和安妮还有联系吗
You still in touch with Annie?
有
Yeah, I am.
我也在找她
Yeah, I been looking for her too.
你有她电话吗
You got her number?
你得让我先和她谈谈
You got to let me talk to her first.
非得这样吗  得了
You gonna be like that? Come on.
饶了我吧
Give me a break.
我有你的电话  查理
I have your number, Charlie.
我会联系你的
I'll be in touch.
我为你骄傲  姑娘
I'm proud of you, girl.
我是说真的
I'm serious.
你做到了
You made it out.
谢谢
Thanks.
你安全了
You're safe.
工作怎么样了
How's work?
很好  博伊特觉得我是内奸
Great. Voight thinks I'm a rat.
真是太好了
Couldn't be better.
那就证明给他看你不是
Just prove to him that you're not.
我一直在努力
I've been trying.
我有几小时时间
I have a couple hours.
这个我们谈过了
We talked about this.
我已经在找自己住的地方了
I'm looking for my own place right now.
我发誓
I swear.
而且我们很快就可以告诉孩子了
And we're gonna tell the kids soon.
很好  那等你做到了...
Okay, well, when that happens--
米娅  我们会在一起的
Mia, we're gonna be together.
你得坚信这一点
You must believe that.
请你不要为了我这么做
Don't do this for me, please,
她会拿走你的一切的
because she is gonna take you for everything that you have.
我会处理的
I've got it all worked out.
等你处理好了再来告诉我
Let me know when you do.
好吧
Okay.
我想到一个方法
I've figured out a way
能让我值得为你花时间和精力
to make you worth my time and effort.
很好
Well, that's great.
我要你从这条街上赚取的所有收益的25%
25%...Everything that you take off the street.
看来我也没得选  所以...
Well, it doesn't look like I have much of a choice, so...
成交
all right.
如果你想整我
If you try to screw me
或者克扣收益  给我下套
or shortchange me or set me up,
我有的是办法可以整你
I have five bear traps set,
你肯定逃不过去的
and you will not make it out alive.
知道了
I get it.
弗朗西斯科·埃雷迪亚
Francisco Heredia.
盯紧他
Get a good look at him.
开火前  我们一定要
Now we obviously want Munoz first
先活捉穆尼奥斯
before any shots are fired.
抓捕埃雷迪亚是第二目标
Getting Heredia in custody is a secondary objective.
到时鱼龙混杂  人流量大
It's gonna be a big crowd, lots of moving parts,
所以都提高警惕
so keep your eyes and ears open.
好了
All right.
吉恩  你过来
Hey, Jin, come here.
昨晚我失态了
I was out of line last night.
不  你没有
No, you weren't, man.
来
Come here.
我爱你
I love you.
喂  喂  喂
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
你也得说你爱我啊
You got to tell me you love me back,
要不然我看起来多傻啊
otherwise I look like an idiot.
快点  老兄
Come on, man.
我也爱你  埃尔文
I love you too, Alvin.
-行了吧  -行了  谢了
- All right? - Yeah. Thanks.
感觉好吗
Is that good?
怎么了
What's up?
最近内务部的人在打我们的主意
We got I.A. sniffing around here lately.
我要你帮我盯着萨姆纳
I want you to keep an eye on Sumner for me.
你一旦发现是她泄密
You get anything that shows that she's a pipeline,
马上告诉我
I want to hear about.
明白
You got it.
就这样
That's it.
埃雷迪亚刚到
Heredia just arrived.
盯紧雕塑旁台上那个卖花的
Keep your eye on the florist on stage near the statue.
有枪
Gun.
开枪了  开枪了
Shots fired! Shots fired!
发生什么事了
What's happened?
他不可能一下放倒两边保镖
There is no way that he got both guards!
看得到二个开枪的人在哪里了吗
Any visual on the second muzzle flash?
埃尔文  霍斯特德  瞄准他了吗
Alvin, Halstead, you got this guy?
目标弯腰了  不在射击范围内
Target ducked down. He's out of sight.
无法锁定目标  不能瞄准
Can't get a lock. No clear shot.
过来  来这  快点
Come on. Come over here. Come on.
-弯腰  -压低
- Stay down! - Get down.
压低  压低
Get down. Get down.
找出穆尼奥斯
Find Munoz!
我看到穆尼奥斯了
I have eyes on Munoz!
借过  借过  借过
Move, move, move, move!
能瞄准吗
Do you have the shot?
不行  从我这个角度看他刚好被挡住了
Negative. He's blocked from this position.
快啊
Come on.
快点
我瞄准穆尼奥斯了
I have Munoz.
开枪
Fire.
快点  快点  快跑
Come on, come on, move, move!
明白  局长
You got it, Commander.
我会传达的
Well, I will pass it along.
刚才是佩里局长
That was Commander Perry.
他问为什么要开火
He wants to know why shots had to be fired.
他的意思就是"干得好"
So much for "nice job."
如果佩里哪天这么说了
The day Perry says that,
我会请大家去KTV
I will take everyone out for karaoke.
我倒想看看这一幕
Ha. I'd pay to see that.
你准备唱什么  老大
What are you gonna sing, boss?
《My Way》
My Way.
你以为是《Love Shack》吗
You were expecting Love Shack?
我不知道
I don't know.
[西语]
是吧  安东尼奥
Si, Antonio?
带他走
I want him out of here.
我们可说好了的
Hey, we had a deal!
走之前我要见莉娜和我儿子
I get to hold Lina and my son before I go.
马上带他走
Get him out of here now.
我的承诺  我会兑现
I made a deal. I keep my word.
怎么了
What's up?
我长话短说
So I need to keep this quick
要不然博伊特会怀疑我去哪了
or Voight's gonna wonder where I am.
你干得很好
You're doing great,
但现在是非常时刻
but right now, more than ever,
我要你时刻关注博伊特的电话
I need you to stay on top of Voight's phone calls,
邮件  行踪  一切消息
his emails, his whereabouts, everything.
每周五我需要一份
I want a full work-up on him
对他全方位调查的详细报告
to be conveyed in a comprehensive report
只给我一人
that goes to me and only to me every Friday.
明白  好
Yeah. Okay.
你父亲最近怎么样
How's your father doing?
好多了  谢谢
Better, thanks.
我很高兴我能帮上忙
I'm glad I could help with that.
我能走了吗
Can I go now?
当然可以
Sure.
快点  速度解决
Come on. Let's make it quick.
为人父母是世界上最幸福的事
There's nothing like being a father,
是不是  安东尼奥
is there, Antonio?
我爱你  儿子[西语]
Te quiero, hijo.
我的爱[西语]
Mi amor.
过来
Come on.
好了  够了
All right, that's enough.
我爱你  我的爱[西语]
Te quiero, mi amor.
你找我
You wanted to see me?
查理·普列塞回来做什么
What's Charlie Pugliese doing back in town?
我不知道  但我会处理的
I don't know, but I will handle it.
原本的交易是
The deal was,
我带你进来  他就得远离伊利诺斯州
I take you in, he stays out of Illinois.
我说了我会处理的
Like I said, I will handle it.
不要走回头路  艾琳
Don't go backward, Erin.
有警员遇袭
We got officers down!
看见什么了吗
You see anything?
-没有  什么都没有  -我去左边
- No. Nothing. - I'll go left.
-没有人  -安东尼奥也遇袭了
- No visual. - Antonio's down!
-汉克  -快叫救护车
- Hank? - Somebody call an ambulance!
呼叫指挥中心
10-1, squad!
警员中枪了
Officer shot,
在21区警署门口
21st district at the roll up!
挺住  挺住
Come on. Come on!